Finding aid for the Albert Kahn Associates records, 1825-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Marketing Photographs, 1902-2007
  - Oakland Hospital - Union and Peoples National Bank
    - Olds Motor Works, Engineering Building, Lansing, MI, (1938), Job No. 1715 (Box 131)
    - Onan Corporation, Service and Training Center, Fridley, MN, (1979), Job No. 2321-A (Box 131)
    - Orchestra Hall, Façade Study, Detroit, MI, Job No. 4983-P (Box 131)
    - Our Lady of Victory's Care, Boiler House, Lackawanna, NY, (1948), Job No. 2026 (Box 131)
    - Owen Building, Detroit, MI, (1907), Job No. 306 (Box 131)
    - Owens-Illinois, HQ Office Building, Perrysburg, OH, Job No. 2958 (Box 131)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Exteriors, Detroit, MI, (1940-1947), Job No. 201 (Box 131)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Office Building, Detroit, MI, (1915-1939), Job No. 201-E (Box 131)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, "Jewel Box" Showroom, Detroit, MI, (1947), Job No. 201-MN (Box 131)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Building No. 10, Detroit, MI, (1903-1910), Job No. 277, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Toledo Division, Propeller Test Building, Dynamometer Test Building, Toledo, OH, (1944-1949), Job No. 1946-A, B (Box 132)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Administration and Sales Building, Chicago, IL, (1948-1950), Job No. 1991-A (Box 132)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Zone Office and Warehouse, Atlanta, GA, (1949), Job No. 2047 (Box 132)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Mound Road Plant, Macomb County, MI, (1951-1954), Job No. 2074 (Box 132)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Mound Road Plant, Boiler House, Macomb County, MI, (1953), Job No. 2074-C (Box 132)
    - Packard Motor Car Company, Office Building and Test Hangar, Flatrock, Toledo, OH, (1944), Job No. P-2296 (Box 132)
    - Paige Motor Car Company, Jewett Plant, Detroit, MI, (1914), Job No. 797 (Box 132)
    - Paige Motor Car Company, Administration Building, Detroit, MI, Job No. 797-M (Box 132)
    - Palmer Office and Store Building, Detroit, MI, (1910), Job No. 417 (Box 132)
    - Palms Apartment House, Detroit, MI, (1902), Job No. 95 (Box 132)
    - Parke Davis and Company, Building No. 64, Detroit, MI, (1940), Job No. 1434 (Box 132)
    - Parke Davis and Company, Biological Building No. 65, Detroit, MI, (1938-1940), Job No. 1434-AL (Box 132)
    - Parke Davis and Company, Animal House, Arsenical Building, Detroit, MI, (1941-1946), Job No. 1434-AO, AV (Box 132)
    - Parke Davis and Company, Research Building Alterations, Detroit, MI, (1941), Job No. 1434-AQ (Box 132)
    - Parke Davis and Company, Clinical Data Handling Addition, Ann Arbor, MI, (1987), Job No. 2393 (Box 132)
    - Parke Davis and Company, 6-Story Manufacturing Building, Detroit, MI, (1946), Job No. P-2453 (Box 132)
    - Peninsular Stove Company, Detroit, MI, (1926), Job No. 1364 (Box 132)
    - People's Community Hospital, Western Wayne County, Eloise, MI, (1944-1945), Job No. 1945 (Box 132)
    - People's Outfitting Company, Store Building, Detroit, MI, Job No. 676 (Box 132)
    - People's Outfitting Company, Store Front Alterations, Dearborn, MI, (1947), Job No. 1477-C (Box 132)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, Rotogravure Building, Philadelphia, PA, (1945-1949), Job No. 1973 (Box 132)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, Newspaper Plant Garage, Philadelphia, PA, (1945-1949), Job No. 1973-A (Box 132)
    - Phoenix Club House, John R and Erskine, Detroit, MI, Job No. 266 (Box 132)
    - Phoenix Golf Club, Redford, MI, (1914), Job No. 625 (Box 132)
    - Pierson Apartments, Woodward and Adelaide, Detroit, MI, (1910), Job No. 65 (Box 132)
    - Planetree, Office Renovation, Derby, CT, (2007) (Box 132)
    - Plymouth Streetscape, Master Plan, Plymouth, MI (Box 132)
    - Pontiac Motor Division, General Motors Corporation, Administrative Building, Pontiac, MI, (1947) (Box 132)
    - Pontiac Motor Division, General Motors Corporation, Pontiac, MI, (1946-1954), Job No. 1402 (Box 132)
    - Pontiac Motor Division, General Motors Corporation, Service Parts Building, Administration Building, Engineering Building, Pontiac, MI, (1945-1951), Job No. 1402 AC, AD, 2 folders (Box 132)
    - Pontiac Motor Division, General Motors Corporation, Pontiac, MI, (1944-1948), Job No. 1402-AE, S, W (Box 132)
    - Pontiac Motor Division, General Motors Corporation, Additions to Foundry, Addition to North End of Personnel Building, Pontiac, MI, (1954), Job No. 1402-BG, BJ (Box 132)
    - Pontiac Motor Division, General Motors Corporation, Service Parts and Storage Building, Gun Plant, Pontiac, MI, (1941-1944), Job No. 1900 (Box 132)
    - Poudre Valley Health System, Harmony Campus ACC/MOB Complex, Fort Collins, CO, Job Nos. 2687/2650 (Box 132)
    - Precision Computing, Acheson Ventures, Port Huron, MI, Job No. 2900-X (Box 132)
    - Proctor and Gamble Company, Great Miami River Project, Research Building, Colerain Township, Hamilton City, OH, (1952-1953), Job No. 2055, 3 folders (Box 132)
    - Providence Journal, Newspaper Plant, Providence, RI, Job No. 1639 (Box 132)
    - Providence Medical Center, Helen DeRoy Cancer Center, Southfield, MI, Job No. 2333-J (Box 132)
    - Providence Medical Center, DePaul Center Expansion, Southfield, MI, Job No. 2333-K (Box 132)
    - Providence Medical Center, Heart Institute Renovation, Southfield, MI, Job No. 2333-R (Box 132)
    - Providence Medical Center, Medical Office Building Expansion, Novi, MI, Job No. 2466-A, M (Box 133)
    - Providence Medical Center, Second Floor Short Stay/Interim OB, Novi, MI, (1988), Job No. 2466-H (Box 133)
    - Providence Medical Center, Phase 1C, Novi, MI, (1996), Job No. 2466-J (Box 133)
    - Providence Medical Center, Assarian Cancer Center, Novi, MI, (1999), Job No. 2466-L (Box 133)
    - Providence Medical Center, Building Addition Renderings, Farmington Hills, MI, Job No. 6251 (Box 133)
    - Radio Corporation of America, Plant Addition, Indianapolis, IN, (1939-1947), Job No. 1802 (Box 133)
    - Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1941-1944), Job No. 1843 F, K (Box 133)
    - Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corporation, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1942-1944), Job No. 1843-L (Box 133)
    - Ranger Aircraft Engines Division, Ranger, MA, (1940), Job No. P-1938 (Box 133)
    - Rehabilitation Institute of Metropolitan Detroit, Detroit, MI, (1955-1958), Job No. 2113 (Box 133)
    - Rehabilitation Institute, Inc., Sixth, Seventh, and Eighth Floor Addition, Detroit, MI, (1966-1971), Job No. 2113-H (Box 133)
    - Rehabilitation Institute, Inc., Investigation of Mechanical System, Replacement of HVAC Systems, Detroit, MI, (1983), Job No. 2113-L, Q (Box 133)
    - Remington Rand, Administration Building, (1962), Job No. P-3240 (Box 133)
    - Republic Aviation Corporation, Airplane Factory, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1940-1941), Job No. 1878, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Republic Aviation Corporation, Airplane Factory, Boiler House, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1941), Job No. 1878-A (Box 133)
    - Republic Aviation Corporation, Experimental and Engineering Building, Farmingdale, Long Island, NY, (1956), Job No. 1878-C (Box 133)
    - Republic Steel Corporation, 96 Inch Continuous Strip Mall, Cleveland, OH, (1937-1938), Job No. 1743 (Box 133)
    - Republic Steel Corporation, Welfare Building, Cleveland, OH, (1938), Job No. 1743-B (Box 133)
    - Richman Brothers Clothing Store, Detroit, MI, Job No. 1596 (Box 133)
    - Robbins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Personnel Building, Brooklyn, NY, (1941), Job No. 1860-A (Box 133)
    - Robbins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Compressor House, Boiler House, Brooklyn, NY, (1941-1942), Job No. 1860-B, C (Box 133)
    - Robbins Dry Dock and Repair Company, Manufacturing and Storage Building, Brooklyn, NY, (1942), Job No. 1860-C (Box 133)
    - Rochester Times Union, Gannett Newspapers, Press Building Addition, Rochester, NY, (1949-1951), Job No. 2052 (Box 133)
    - Rollman Brothers Store, Cincinnati, OH, Job No. 1056 (Box 133)
    - Saginaw Malleable Iron Foundry Division, General Motors Corporation, Foundry Building, Danville, IL, (1943-1945), Job No. 1947 (Box 133)
    - Saginaw Malleable Iron Foundry Division, General Motors Corporation, Foundry Building, Boiler House, Danville, IL, (1945), Job No. 1947-B (Box 133)
    - Saginaw Malleable Iron Foundry Division, General Motors Corporation, Propane Pump House, Danville, IL, (1945), Job No. 1947-C (Box 133)
    - Saginaw Malleable Iron Foundry Division, General Motors Corporation, Office Building, Danville, IL, (1945), Job No. 1957-A (Box 133)
    - Saginaw News, Newspaper Plant, Saginaw, MI, Job No. 1680 (Box 133)
    - Saint Francis Home for Orphan Boys, Detroit, MI, Job No. 729 (Box 133)
    - Saint John Health, Romeo Plank Center, Macomb Township, MI, (1998), Job No. 2587-A (Box 133)
    - Saint John Health, ADT Center, Macomb, MI, Job No. 2871-C (Box 133)
    - Saint Joseph Hospital, Addition and Alterations, Mount Clemens, MI, (1958-1962), Job No. 2061-D (Box 133)
    - Saint Joseph Hospital, Chapel Addition and Alterations, Mount Clemens, MI, (1950-1962), Job No. 2061-F (Box 133)
    - Saint Joseph Hospital of Mount Clemens, Inc., Southwest Building Addition, Sterling Heights, MI, (1935 1988), Job No. 2327-C (Box 133)
    - Saint Mary's Hospital, Livonia, MI, (1999), Job No. 2536 (Box 133)
    - Saint Mary's Hospital, Expansion Project, Livonia, MI, (1999), Job No. 2536-B (Box 133)
    - Saint Vincent's Hospital, Fourth Floor Diagnostics, Birmingham, AL, Job No. 20100-01 (Box 133)
    - Scherer Estate, Office Building, Detroit, MI, Job No. 1322 (Box 133)
    - Schust Company, Warehouse, Fourth Avenue and Hudson, Detroit, MI, (1924), Job No. 1193 (Box 133)
    - James E. Scripps Library and Art Gallery, Detroit, MI, (1898), Job No. 152 (Box 134)
    - Security Trust Company, Bank Building, Detroit, MI, (1945), Job No. 1140 (Box 134)
    - Seiberling Rubber Company, Factory Building, Barberton, OH, (1945-1946), Job No. 1935 (Box 134)
    - Seiberling Rubber Company, Office Building, Barberton, OH, (1943-1946), Job No. 1935-A (Box 134)
    - Shaarey Zedek Congregation, Synagogue Center, Southfield, MI, (1961-1967), Job No. 2138, 3 folders (Box 134)
    - Shaw Walker Company, Office Building, Muskegon, MI, (1913), Job No. 575 (Box 134)
    - Dr. J. Donald Sheets, Clinic Building, Highland Park, MI, (1963), Job No. 2164 (Box 134)
    - Sherwin-Williams Company, Chemical Products Building, Chicago, IL, (1941), Job No. 1845 (Box 134)
    - Sherwin-Williams Company, Warehouse, Chicago, IL, (1940-1941), Job No. 1845-A (Box 134)
    - Siegel Building, Woodward and Clifford, S.S. Kresge 5 and 10 Store, Detroit, MI, (1915), Job No. 500 (Box 134)
    - Siegel, B., Residence, Detroit, MI, Job No. 582 (Box 134)
    - Thomas Henry Simpson Memorial Institute, Ann Arbor, MI, (1927), Job No. 1239 (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Detroit, MI, (1951-1974), Job No. 1985 (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Kitchen, Detroit, MI, (1972), Job No. 1985 (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Medical Coronary Intensive Care Unit, Detroit, MI, (1975), Job No. 1985-AC (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Samuel and Isabelle Friedman Laboratory, Detroit, MI, (1974), Job No. 1985-AH (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, New Entrance -- Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation Center, Detroit, MI, (1975), Job No. 1985-AW (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Detroit, MI, (1948-1977), Job No. 1985-B, 5 folders (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Perinatal Center, Detroit, MI, (1978-1983), Job No. 1985-BG, 4 folders (Box 134)
    - Sinai Hospital, Shapero School of Nursing, Detroit, MI, (1954-1957), Job No. 1985-D (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Addition, Detroit, MI, (1957-1964), Job No. 1985-E, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Medical Library, Detroit, MI, (1962-1966), Job No. 1985-O (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Medical Research Building, Detroit, MI, (1963), Job No. 1985-P (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Auditorium and Conference Center, Detroit, MI, (1965-1969), Job No. 1985-Q (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, New Research Building, Detroit, MI, (1985), Job No. 1985-RR-25 (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Auditorium and Conference Center, Radiotherapy Building, Detroit, MI, (1976), Job No. 1985-R-60 (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Perinatal Center, Detroit, MI, (1978), Job No. 1985-R-71 (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Renovation of North Wing Entrance, Detroit, MI, (1981), Job No. 1985-R-96 (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Expanded Patient Care Facilities, Detroit, MI, (1965-1975), Job No. 1985-S (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Radiotherapy Center, Detroit, MI, (1964-1968), Job No. 1985-W (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Center for Continued Care, Detroit, MI, (1968), Job No. 1985-Y (Box 135)
    - Sinai Hospital, Shapero School of Nursing Addition, Detroit, MI, (1969), Job No. P-3498 (Box 135)
    - C.F. Smith Company, Office Building, Detroit, MI, Job No. 800-B (Box 135)
    - Southeastern Junior High School, Battle Creek, MI, Job No. 1593 (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Health System, Site Analysis, Lansing, MI, (1994), Job No. 2529-A (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Health System, Healing Garden, Lansing, MI, Job No. 2529-BE (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Health System, Seventh Floor Neumann Wing Addition, Lansing, MI, (2004), Job No. 2529-BQ (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Health System, Neumann Wing Addition, Lansing, MI, Job No. 2529-W (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Health System, Data Center, Lansing, MI, (1999), Job No. 2607 (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Hospital System, Professional Building, Site Plans, Lansing, MI, Job No. 2529-D (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Hospital, ACC/MOB Parking Deck, Lansing, MI, Job No. 2529-E (Box 135)
    - Sparrow Hospital System, Master Site Model, Lansing, MI, Job No. 4828 (Box 135)
    - Spence Engineering Company, Office Building, Baton Rouge, LA, (1944), Job No. P-2295 (Box 135)
    - Spietz and Worch Company, United Cigar Manufacturing Company Branch, Detroit, MI, Job No. 419 (Box 135)
    - Standard Accident Insurance Company, Detroit, MI, Job No. 952 (Box 135)
    - Standard Club, Chicago, IL, Job No. 1174 (Box 135)
    - Frederick Stearns and Company, Detroit, MI, (1929), Job No. 622 (Box 135)
    - Stinson Aircraft Division, Aviation Manufacturing Corporation, Factory and Office, Nashville, TN, (1939-1940), Job No. 1828 (Box 135)
    - Stinson Aircraft Division, Aviation Manufacturing Corporation, Office Building, Nashville, TN, (1940), Job No. 1828-A (Box 135)
    - Studebaker Company, South Bend, IN, (1924-1925), Job No. 1066 (Box 135)
    - Suomi College, Master Plan, Hancock, MI, (1990), Job No. 2448 (Box 135)
    - Swift, C.M., Residence, Grosse Pointe, MI, Job No. 168 (Box 135)
    - Talon Development Group, Tower Automotive, Novi, MI, Job No. 2731 (Box 135)
    - Taylorcraft Aviation Corporation, Aircraft Plant, Office Building, Alliance, OH, (1940-1941), Job No. 1859 (Box 135)
    - Temple Beth El, Detroit, MI, (1903), Job No. 136 (Box 135)
    - Temple Beth El, Detroit, MI, (1945), Job No. 821 (Box 135)
    - Thompson Products, Inc., Manufacturing Plant, Manufacturing Building Addition, Euclid, OH, (1941-1951), Job No. 1885 Q (Box 135)
    - Thompson Products, Inc., Office Building, Euclid, OH, (1941-1942), Job No. 1885-A (Box 135)
    - Thompson Products, Inc., Boiler House, Euclid, OH, (1942-1944), Job No. 1885-B (Box 135)
    - Thompson Products, Inc., Personnel and Service Building, Euclid, OH, (1942-1945), Job No. 1885-L (Box 135)
    - Thurber Garage, Detroit, MI, Job No. 1120-B (Box 135)
    - Todd Hoboken Dry Goods, Tietjen and Lang Dry Docks Company, Plant and Fabricating Shop, Hoboken, NJ, (1943), Job No. 1876-A (Box 135)
    - Toledo Scale Company, Toledo, OH, (1939-1948), Job No. 1799 (Box 135)
    - Toyota Technical Services, Toyota Technical Center Office Building Expansion, Ann Arbor, MI, (1999), Job No. 2635 (Box 136)
    - Trane Company, Engineering and Office Building, La Crosse, WI, (1957-1965), Job No. 2107-A (Box 136)
    - Trane Company, Acoustics Laboratory, La Crosse, WI, (1966), Job No. 2107-F (Box 136)
    - Trane Company, Administrative Building, La Crosse, WI, (1957-1969), Job No. 2107-G, 3 folders (Box 136)
    - Traverse City, Power and Generating Facilities Alterations and Additions, Traverse City, MI, (1965-1969), Job No. 2149-A (Box 136)
    - Travis Pointe Country Club, Country Club Renovation, Ann Arbor, MI, (2004), Job No. 8077-C (Box 136)
    - Trinity Medical Center, Hammes Company, Exterior and Interior Renderings, Moline, IL, Job No. 2542 (Box 136)
    - Trinity Medical Center, Hammes Company, Seventh Street Campus, Moline, IL, Job No. 2542 (Box 136)
    - Trinity Medical Center, Chesterfield Township, MI, Job Nos. 2692, 2693 (Box 136)
    - Trinity Regional Health System, Trinity at Terrace Park Replacement Hospital, Bettendorf, IA, Job No. 2747-A (Box 136)
    - Trizec Corporation, Office Building, West Grand Boulevard and Second, Detroit, MI, (1978), Job No. 2295-A (Box 136)
    - Truscon Steel Company, Detroit, MI, (1916), Job No. 722 (Box 136)
    - UAW-Chrysler, National Training Center, Detroit, MI, Job No. 2459 (Box 136)
    - UAW-GM, Human Resource Center, Auburn Hills, MI, Job No. 2490 (Box 136)
    - Union and Peoples National Bank, Jackson, MI, Job No. 1425 (Box 136)
  - United Aircraft Corporation - University of Alabama, Birmingham
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division, East Hartford, CT, (1930-1947), Job No. 1509 (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division, Garage, East Hartford, CT, Job No. 1509 (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Aircraft Division, Offices, East Hartford, CT, Job No. 1509 (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, Pratt and Whitney Division, East Hartford, CT, (1937-1950), Job Nos. 1519, 1509 (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Factory Addition, East Hartford, CT, (1941), Job No. 1509-AY (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, New Hangar Office Building, East Hartford, CT, (1940), Job No. 1509-BC (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Addition to East Side of Present Factory Building, East Hartford, CT, (1941), Job No. 1509-BG (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Eight to Sixteen Foot Product Test Houses, East Hartford, CT, (1942), Job No. 1509-BS (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Converting Boiler Plant from Oil to Coal, East Hartford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1509-CH, CK (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Supercharger Test Houses, East Hartford, CT, (1943), Job No. 1509-CL (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Two 24 Foot Diameter Experiment Test Cells, East Hartford, CT, (1943-1944), Job No. 1509-CM (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, East Hartford, CT, (1946), Job No. 1509-CW, CX (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Engine Development Laboratory, East Hartford, CT, (1946-1958), Job No. 1509-DO (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, X-ray Building, East Hartford, CT, (1947), Job No. 1509-DQ (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Research Department, Burner Test Rig, East Hartford, CT, (1948-1950), Job No. 1509-DS (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Boiler House Extension, East Hartford, CT, (1951), Job No. 1509-DX (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Eight 20 Foot Production Test Cells and Carburetor Air Box Building, East Hartford, CT, (1952), Job No. 1509-EA (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Computation Laboratory and Office Building Extension, East Hartford, CT, (1956-1958), Job No. 1509-FB (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Willgoos Laboratory Engine Development Facilities II, East Hartford, CT, (1957-1958), Job No. 1509-FC (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Power House Addition, East Hartford, CT, (1965), Job No. 1509-FV (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, East Hartford, CT, (1936-1937), Job No. 1509-L, M (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Test House, East Hartford, CT, (1937-1938), Job No. 1509-O (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, 18 Foot Test Houses, East Hartford, CT, (1939), Job No. 1509-X (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Engineering Building, East Hartford, CT, (1937-1943), Job No. 1509-Z, AC, CE (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Factory Building, East Hartford, CT, (1930-1936), Job No. 1519 (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Office Building, East Hartford, CT, (1930-1944), Job Nos. 1519, 1804-F (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, Engineering Building Addition, East Hartford, CT, (1936-1938), Job No. 1519-G (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, Temporary Office Building, East Hartford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1519-L (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, East Hartford, CT, (1937), Job No. 1519-M (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, South Extension to Hot Forming Operations and Southwest Extensions to Factory Building, East Hartford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1519-N, O (Box 136)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, Two 33 Foot Square Propeller Test Houses, East Hartford, CT, (1945-1946), Job No. 1519-Q (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Hamilton Standard Division, Southeast Extension to Factory Building, East Hartford, CT, (1948), Job No. 1519-S (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Addition to South Side of Hamilton Standard Building, East Hartford, CT, (1951-1952), Job No. 1519-W (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Pratt and Whitney Division, Test Houses, East Hartford, CT, (1939), Job No. 1519-Y (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804 (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Vought-Sikorsky Division, Factory Building Additions, Stratford, CT, (1939-1943), Job No. 1804-A, B (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Office Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-F (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Factory Extension, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-G (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Electric Distribution System Additions, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-K (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Scrap Segregation Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-L (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Paint Storage Building, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-M (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, West Employees' Entrance, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-N (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Fire House, Stratford, CT, (1944), Job No. 1804-O (Box 137)
    - United Aircraft Corporation, Chance-Vought Aircraft Division, Cafeteria Rearrangements, Stratford, CT, (1944-1945), Job No. 1804-R (Box 137)